Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during
the filming of this series
Söğüt
Episode 117
Osman.
He who crosses borders
does not live long.
I will find the gold(s) and bring it to you.
You will release the sons of Beys.
Temporarily, if necessary.
Commander Nayman.
We did what you asked of us.
Gold was on the way.
Something must have happened.
We will find and bring it.
Free our children.
If necessary, we will give you more gold.
Don't
Don't.
If you kill them...
Then you will not be able to take gold.
Forgive them now.
Forgive them so that we may all win.
I have cured your son.
And in return, you plan a game for me.
I will kill the sons of Beys.
You have time until tomorrow evening.
You will bring me the gold, Osman.
Otherwise, the sons of Beys will die.
Not only them...
I will take your children from you too.
One soul is more valuable than
a thousand gold coins.
I'll get that gold for you.
You won't touch my sons, nor
the sons of my Beys.
I keep my promises unlike you.
If there is no gold, there
will be no children.
This is my last word.
Take them.
Don't ever worry.
I will bring your sons to you safely.
Don't worry.
Rest assured.
For now, stay safe.
Osman Bey.
Stop!
Are you going like this
without an account?
Yakup Bey.
If one hair on my son's
head is hurt...
I swear, I, first you and then
your followers....
Continue.
Continue so that no difference remains
between you and the unbeliever who has gone.
Osman Bey.
Do you have gold?
Let's say I have it.
Many innocent people have
a right to that gold.
But you feared for your lives
and wanted to pay the tax.
It turns out that you are not as
brave as you are, Candar Bey.
Do you think we are
afraid for ourselves?
We fear for our children.
We fear for our people.
He who fears death
does not remain free.
And whoever is not free, there is no
difference between him and the dead.
Well, when your son was
martyred on the battlefield...
did your heart ache?
Or would you be proud of it?
Martyrdom is definitely
the greatest status.
But where is the fight?
Where is the field?
Here is the fight and here is the field!
The oppressors want us to
be under their command!
But many valiants are against this.
I will solve this.
How?
I'll find the gold and give it to Nayman.
I will return your children to you.
Don't ever worry.
So be it as you say, Osman Bey.
Let it be as you say.
As I said, I hope
you have nothing to do with the gold issue.
Be comfortable and reassured.
I will return them to you.
I will be your end, Olof.
I will bury you and your soldiers, Turgut.
I am content to lie beside my warriors.
But I wonder, are
you ready to die?
Come here.
Olof, we have to go.
- Olof.
- No!
Olof, we can't win, walk!
We will fight.
We must fight, Olof.
To earn the love of the God.
Olof!
Walk!
Come on, walk, Olof.
Walk.
No!
- Olof!
- Stop!
Come on, valiants.
My soldiers!
We'll get revenge, Olof.
They are coming.
You go from here.
Come on!
You come with me.
There is no news from my Bey yet.
What are we going to do, Konur Alp?
What if Nayman played a game
for my Bey when he didn't get the gold?
Does he not know then that
he will never be able to have it?
Definitely knows.
But Nayman's actions
just don't make sense.
Brother Konur, shall we go
to Söğüt to see?
Nobody will go anywhere.
Our job is to wait for our Bey here.
We'll wait.
Now...
Send messengers to the observers in
the vicinity.
To watch the place well.
We must have an eye behind us.
If a guest comes without an invitation,
he will get his due from our swords.
We'll do what you say, brother, but what are
we going to do with this gold?
Let my Bey come first.
He is the one who will say what to do.
Good.
Stop it, Olof.
Olof.
They are here.
Run!
Run, run, run!
Dan.
No, Olof.
I can't leave Dan.
We are few in number.
Dan.
Turgut.
Your death will be by my hands, Turgut.
People like you only
kill innocent people.
They take innocent lives.
Come here.
Attack!
I will cut off your head
with my own hands, Turgut
Doesn't sound like you crushing
and killing the weak, does it?
The fate of people like you is to obey to
us and death.
My Bey, what are we going
to do with these two?
These two will do us good, Acar.
Osman Bey thought of a good
move for them.
Now take these two dogs.
You won't die easily, Frigg.
You are in my hands until you speak.
You will tell the Beys all of
İsmihan's tricks one by one.
I won't tell.
I won't tell, you can't make me talk.
Do you trust Olof?
If he was going to save you, he would
have saved you a long time ago.
Olof will come and I will kill you all.
I know how to make you talk.
Right now we need
her alive, Bengi Hatun.
And I will send you to
your brother's side.
Bengi Hatun.
Leave me.
Leave me to kill her.
You're not going near Frigg anymore.
You're not going into this cage.
Alçiçek.
Alçiçek, I don't know
what to say, daughter.
What is happening?
If I had known this would happen,
I would never have done this.
Now, you can't meet your
loved one because of me.
Speak clearly, mother, I don't understand.
I couldn't kill Frigg.
Now if Frigg talks,
Osman Bey will know everything.
About me, Esma and İsmihan.
What are you saying?
Because you wanted to...
I pulled Frigg into a trap.
But I made a game and sent word to frigg
She knew about the trap.
She wouldn't have been
caught, but they caught her.
If she speaks...
you won't
be able to meet with Aktemur...
he will cut off my head,
your father's head, and all of our heads.
Osman Bey will not forgive us.
You said you didn't know
about the poison.
I did not know.
So, tell Osman Bey, and
he will understand.
No one will believe us after they learn
that Esma gave the poison.
We have to get Frigg out of
the tribe before she speaks.
Otherwise, everything will end.
But who will do this?
The ladies' eyes are on me.
I will do it.
Leave me, I'll get out on my own
Good.
Don't take your eyes off her, Alçiçek.
I will save you.
But do not speak.
What?
Why?
My mother sent me.
It is the order of Mother Sultan.
I have to do this in
order to marry Aktemur.
Love...
Love.
You set me free for love, right?
Shut up and listen to me.
If we hand over the gold to the people,
they will rest, my bey.
We will not hand over the gold to the people.
Why?
is there a problem?
Nayman has kidnapped Beys' sons.
If we don't give him the gold...
Then he will kill them.
And what shall we do now, my Bey?
Will we obey to these infidels?
Nayman is like a dam built in
front of the Turkmens.
We will tear down that dam
and cut off its head.
But until then, our movements
will be kept confidential.
Our swords are sharp and
our strength is permanent.
Well, my bey.
Are we really going to
give them the gold?
We'll give them gold.
Now, hear me well.
Turgut.
Osman.
I will take your souls for
what you took from me.
The end that awaits you...
will be your death.
We got through them, Olof
Come on.
Commander Olof.
For the sake of the great Jesus, your
wound is very serious.
We must wrap it.
We won't stop.
We'll take Dan and Frigg.
Have mercy on us, O great Jesus.
If only we bandaged the wound
first and then we'd go get them.
We've lost a lot
of men, Olof.
We have to go to İnegöl.
We take support from there
and attack them again.
But now...
Shall we go back?
Isn't it better that we take
prisoners from them?
Sister, read your prayers and don't
get involved in matters you don't know.
Had it not been for my prayers, your
blood would have watered the earth.
Shut up!
We'll go back to İnegöl!
Good.
I go before you and tell the doctors.
Let the most skilled doctors
dress your wound.
I will not stay and meddle
in matters I do not know.
She can go, Olof
We make too much noise when
we're outnumbered.
It is better for us to disperse.
You and you...
Go with the nun.
Be careful, come on.
We'll give the gold to Olof.
But not real gold.
The fake ones.
Turgut Bey wanted to hit Olof
for a long time. Is he alive?
News has come from Turgut.
Olof somehow escaped.
My Bey.
As long as we hand
him the fake gold...
Why even give it to Olof?
Wouldn't it be better if we hand him over to Nayman directly and take the Beys' sons?
If we give it to Nayman...
We can only take Beys' sons.
But if we give the gold to Olof...
and we tell Nayman the gold was with Olof...
then, we will win two victories.
And we'll beat the two dogs together.
It is true what you say, my Bey.
Now it's time for us to think about how
to give the gold to Olof.
We'll do this with Frigg.
Ladies will be on it.
Konur.
You will take this gold to the caravansary
in Çamlıpınar.
Olof and Frigg are going to find the gold
as if they've got it.
Your command, my Bey.
My Bey.
Is this game going to fool Nayman?
Will he believe right away?
This depends on
our persuasion ability.
But first let's get into
that dog's hole and then we'll see.
Come on.
Let everyone go to work.
Come on, Alps.
Bala.
Osman Bey sent the gold to the caravansary
in Çamlıpınar.
Good.
I will survive from here.
I will kill you all one by one.
You can't do anything
anymore, Frigg.
Let her go up.
Get out of here, Frigg.
Bengi.
It will be your turn.
I will be back for you all.
Shall we send warriors with her?
Alps!
Take Frigg to Yenişehir first.
Then, go to the caravansary.
I should go too, just in case.
Where are you going, Ayşe Hatun?
We came to take the
bride's box to Yenişehir.
Isn't there someone else to go with them?
May my mother Ayşe stay and I will go.
And you two will solve the rest.
Good.
You've done your first mission as a female
warrior, Alçiçek.
Come on.
Sisters!
Alps!
Come on, let's go.
Osman Bey is coming.
Welcome.
Thank you.
We scattered Olof's armies.
They dispersed into the woods.
Olof ran away, but
I caught his dishonorable brother
You hit Olof hard.
He can go wherever he wants.
Olof's fate is known.
Congratulations on your victory, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
And now I have to tell you.
Say it.
I see that Olof is
never far from Ülgen Hatun.
We attacked him a lot and he
never suspected a thing.
They obviously believed she was a nun.
They respect her.
That's fine, fine.
When we take İnegöl, Ülgen
will be of great use to us.
We hurt Olof.
Now, it's time to beat Nayman
and Olof together.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Take this dog and send him to Yenişehir.
And we're going to Nayman
Your command, my Bey.
Dear brothers...
Something they never
expected will happen.
We'll take the sons first.
And after we take them...
We will destroy the enemy
and move on.
We will cut their flesh to pieces...
until they have no power left
in front of us.
As long as we are united, we won't leave
any power around, Inshallah.
As long as we have brothers
like these behind us...
Nothing will happen to us, thank Allah.
Thank you.
Come on.
Put more observers on the roads leading
to the caravansary, Aykurt.
Nayman's men are everywhere.
Let us take good measures
and reach the caravansary in secret.
We will deliver the boxes to the
caravansary safely, Inshallah.
Warriors, come on.
My Bey must be about to start his campaign.
We must arrive quickly.
We will.
Let's make sure the road
is safe first and we'll get there.
Sir, what are they doing?
They believe that these lands will be
theirs if a bird lands on the nest...
that they are building and
makes a home for itself.
It's a habit.
They tied their future to a bird, then.
Good then.
There are birds' nests around their camp,
shall I target them?
If their prayers was accepted,
the sky would rain bones.
We turned our backs on the truth.
May the birds fly free in our homeland.
Alps!
Let's take a break.
Wait for me, Olof
Wait.
Warriors!
It's a trap!
Come on, from this side.
You smell like a trick, Osman.
One smells oneself first.
Nayman's order is definitive.
He said, "Cut off Osman's head if
he comes empty-handed."
Since Nayman trusts you...
You must not be very smart.
How did you know I
came empty-handed?
I can't see the gold, Osman.
Then the eye of your heart
must be closed, Shaman.
If Nayman campaigns at your word...
Woe to him.
If he's empty-handed, he must
have brought a piece of information, Shaman.
Say, Osman.
Is what you have on your hands
is the blood of the innocent?
It is the blood of a vow.
The offerings do not seek
possession and conquests as we do.
They live to be sacrificial to God.
Where is the gold?
Where are the sons of Beys?
Show me that they are alive.
Then I will tell you where the gold is.
Bring them.
Pray for Mother Sultan.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have released
you before we killed you.
The wedding would be a
dream if they knew the truth.
I made you run so
that they wouldn't know.
Calm down, calm down.
Come on, go now.
But don't you talk.
Never.
I didn't see anything.
Alçiçek...
I will never forget your help.
I have to make them believe.
You're wrong, you look
like your mother.
I liked you, Alçiçek.
Wait for me, Olof, come on.
Osman, where is the gold?
I can not hear you.
If I don't hear
about the place of gold...
I will start killing them by cutting off their ears.
The great Commander Nayman...
is betrayed
Saying this is not that easy.
Speak.
Olof has the golds.
I couldn't hear you.
You heard me.
You heard correctly.
Olof has the golds.
Yenişehir
Snake Frigg got caught.
We found an antidote
to the poison.
Now it's time to find
out who poisoned the tribe.
Don't worry, we'll know that soon, too.
We will know.
Alçiçek is late.
Can I come in?
Come in, Alçiçek.
Alçiçek.
Frigg fell into the game.
Alps have been sent after her.
Alps!
Get up.
Frigg's gone, come on, catch her!
And I learned that gold
is also in the caravansary.
She'll go now and tell Olof.
It's done.
Now keep the promise you
made to me, Alçiçek.
Who poisoned my son?
Tell me, Alçiçek.
You said you'd tell me.
Who did this to my son?
I did.
How do you do this to my son?
They threatened me with my brother,
I had no other solution!
Shut up!
My son was in a bad condition
because of you!
Was this in exchange for
our favor to you, Esma?
Forgive me.
For my brother's soul.
I put the poison.
I got scared after that and backed
off, but I didn't have enough time.
Forgive me, Malhun Hatun, I am very sorry.
Please, forgive me.
If anyone made a mistake, it was me.
I am the one who brought Esma here.
I wish we had never come.
Who gave it to you?
Who gave you the poison?
Did Bengi Hatun give it to you?
Who did this?
Who asked you to do this?
Avcı.
Avcı Bey gave me the poison.
İsmihan did it.
Loyalty is not bought with
gold or intimidation.
You've been betrayed by
Olof who's under your command.
Osman.
If you are planning a game...
No game.
If the gold hadn't come,
you would have tried to attack us.
If we fought...
we'd kill each other.
And that would only benefit Olof.
And he...
It is for this reason
that he took Beys' golds.
Golds are mine.
Mine, Osman!
You will bring me the golds.
I don't fall for Olof's game...
nor for your game.
If I attack Olof now, I will lose my warriors.
As the gold is yours...
Then you will go and fetch it.
Tell me where it is.
It's in the caravansary near Çamlıpınar.
Then you will wait here until I
go and fetch the gold.
No.
I promised Beys that I would bring
their sons to them.
I'll get out of here with Beys' sons.
I will give you gold.
Then...
I'll take your head first, then the gold.
Stop it, Nayman!
Take me prisoner, Nayman.
Then, you run and collect your dirty gold.
If there is a game like you said...
then you cut off my head and it's over.
Give Beys to Osman...
and arrest Turgut.
We'll go.
There was no other solution.
You also know that.
Never worry.
I will get you safe from here.
Yes, I know.
Win for the Turks.
We said fidelity, right?
I sacrifice my life for you
and for this country.
I do.
Tell us, Bengi Hatun.
Tell us what you did behind us.
Did you have a hand
in poisoning my son?
- If you...
- No!
Ask Esma, I learned
when I got to the tribe.
All this was a game from İsmihan.
How do we know you're telling
the truth, Bengi Hatun?
Why should I do such a thing on the morning
when I gave you my daughter?
İsmihan must have taken
advantage of Esma...
to not cooperate with you.
Wasn't there anyone else
who could have poisoned the tribe?
You didn't know about the poison.
We get it.
Well, what about the others?
You worked with the cruels!
Frigg, Olof, İsmihan.
You sat and watched, even though you
knew that İsmihan poisoned the people.
They put my father in the castle
dungeon and you were silent!
Did I have another choice, Bala Hatun?
İsmihan is unlike anyone else.
She can hurt people without thinking.
You threatened to kill my daughter.
Otherwise, am I someone who would
work with people who killed my brother?
There was no strong family
behind me like you.
I'm alone.
I keep this family alive alone.
Do I regret what I did?
Yes.
But I had no other choice.
Understand this firstly.
We now understand.
But Esma will not remain unpunished.
She poisoned my son, she will
definitely be held accountable.
Esma has no guilt.
Get up.
The guilt is all mine.
Alçiçek.
My sister.
My brother!
Esma committed this sin because of me.
Punish me, not her.
We'll talk about this, Bengi Hatun.
We will talk.
Söğüt
Osman will now try to draw
all Beys to his side.
But we will not allow this, Celali.
Your command, Mother Sultan.
Say it, Celali.
How are we going to stop
Nayman, Mother Sultan?
No force can stop Nayman.
Now I will go to Konya to speak with
Sultan Alaeddin about peace.
The future of our land will be determined by the decisions that Sultan Aladdin and I will make.
Your command, Mother Sultan.
Frigg.
Olof!
I will hold everyone who did this
to you accountable!
Frodi.
Frigg.
How?
How did you escape from them?
On the road, let's talk on the road.
Gold, gold is very important to Osman
I heard that while they were talking.
Why?
Why is gold so important?
I don't know, they were all so nervous.
We have to get that gold, Olof
Dan.
They took him.
Turgut took him.
Since gold is very
important to Osman...
They must make a deal with us.
I know where the gold is.
They hide it/them (golds) in
the caravansary near Çamlıpınar.
Hurry up.
Good.
Well, we'll go.
Let's go.
This time, we'll hit Osman
from where he never expected.
Come on, let's go.
İnegöl Castle
No.
No, I can't wait that long.
I will go.
I'll go, however...
Where am I going?
Oh, Ülgen Hatun.
I should have gone.
I should have gone myself
So far they have not come, I fear that
something bad has happened to her.
Look at him.
You will see now.
Cerkutay.
I'm dying, Cerkutay.
I'm dying.
Cerkutay, I'm dying!
Who did this to you?
Tell me one thing before
I go to Allah.
You'll be fine, I'll cure you.
Do you love me?
Tell me about this.
Cerkutay.
I'm dying, I'm dying, answer my question.
Do you love me?
Cerkutay.
Ulgen Hatun.
- I...love...
- You?
Hey, don't pull it off!
Don't pull it, Cerkutay...
Don't pull it, I'll die instantly!
I'll die, don't pull it!
Why are you pulling it?
I will die...
What is this?
I was kidding
Ulgen.
Hey whatever!
Hear what I have to say.
Turgut Bey took dog Dan.
And Olof was shot.
Soon the longing will end, I hope.
Nice.
I was kidding you.
Are you furious?
Eh?
Marmaracik Castle.
Oh Allah, oh my Creator!
What have you done, Alcicek?
What did you do, my daughter?
I did everything just for you two.
You burned us, Alcicek.
You threw us to the fire.
Do you think Ismihan
will let this go unpunished?
You were hesitant.
And I helped you decide
which side to choose.
Daughter.
Do you think Mother Sultan would let us
live if she heard of this? Don't you know?
From now on, you will not stand
with Mother Sultan, but against her.
How so?
You're brave, Alcicek,
but you're ignorant.
I am.
I am ignorant, but I can see who cares
their people, not themself while you can't.
Mother Sultan is selfish,
don't you see that?
She only thinks of herself.
But Osman Bey only thinks of his people.
From now on, you either
side with Osman Bey...
Or forget my abscene.
She talked to you.
Yenisehir
If something happens to my son...
I will demolish Yenişehir over his head!
Talk about the good, Yakup Bey.
Choose your words carefully.
- Don't always talk evil.
- Man, where is the gold?
Didn't we dedicate many alps to protect it?
Apparently Osman Bey stole it.
Basically I never wanted to give it to him.
We die starving or we die fighting,
doesn't matter.
Our campaign was not a brave campaign.
But my son, may Allah protect him from the worst
Attention!
Osman Bey!
Sorry for keeping you waiting, Beys.
Where is my son, Osman Bey?
I brought your children safely.
Boran.
My valiant!
Son!
My child!
Thank you Osman Bey, thank you.
I can't thank you enough,
you shall find peace.
Are you the one who
endangered our children's lives, Osman Bey?
Where is the gold?
Olof has it.
Nayman will hold him accountable.
I brought your children safely.
The account has now been closed.
What are you going to do now, Osman Bey?
I will do what you couldn't do.
I will fight.
Don't do it, Osman Bey.
I will do what a person with a brave heart does
even though they are few.
I let go the Beys who are many but coward.
- Osman Bey.
- You are not right at all, not even slightly.
Don't talk, Yakup Bey.
The war and victory shall be mine.
Goodbye.
Osman Bey.
May Allah open your way.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Eyvallah (Thanks).
Caravansary
near Camlipinar
Osman can't be that imprudent.
Close all places, Frody.
Be careful.
Kill anyone who moves,
whether human or animal.
Osman.
Your death is here, Olof.
Can I, father?
Come on son.
Son.
Don't hurry, son.
Let me, mother.
Hatuns, let him.
Let him.
Let him come, come on.
Come on boy, come on!
Come here.
Come, easy.
Praise be to Allah!
Praise be to Allah.
I can walk, father.
Traitors couldn't reach their goal.
You can, you can do it son.
I also had this feeling
when you walked for the first time.
Praise be to Allah, thank Him very much.
But my arm...
My arm isn't like how it used to be, father.
It'll get better too, son.
You'll be like you used to be, Inshallah.
Stay patienent, Orhan.
Patience leads to soundness.
What did I tell you, son?
You rise so that the state rises.
Come on, come on, slowly, slowly
Come, come here.
Come son, come on, come here.
Son...
- Boran!
- My Bey!
Bring the map and war gear.
- As you order, my Bey.
- Go.
Oh, my son.
Praise be to Allah, Praise be to Allah
I allowed your head to stay on your body
and you set your eyes on my gold, Olof?
I spoke to you in the language you understand.
But it turns out you're a fool!
I heard that the gold
belonged to Osman, Commander
Everything on these lands belongs to me!
Gold and your head included!
Frigg.
I'll take both of them.
The gold you stole will cause your death.
Gold will eat everything.
And you will go where you belong to,
the depth of the sea!
I didn't do wrong to you, Commander
Osman.
We only have one advantage, which is
that Nayman is not in the headquarters.
The only advantage, the only chance.
Nayman's most skilled soldiers
stand around his headquarters.
Even if our number is equal to them...
...I can't guarantee victory
in the event of a battle.
You say that victory is difficult even if
our numbers are equal, right, my Bey?
Plus, their number
is already larger than us.
We've figured everything out, Aktemur.
Now...
They line up at five points
around the headquarters.
Just like this.
There are many Mongol soldiers
at those lines.
Except for one of them.
The number of soldiers here is small.
But they dug trenches on the way.
We'll use that way.
What about our horses?
How will the horses get over those trenches, Osman?
We talked to the builders, they'll build
little birdges that horses can go through.
The Bey of the neighboring tribes will
send their alps to our army.
- Boran.
- My Bey!
Archers will be at your command.
You will shoot the guards.
And then,
when we pass the bridges...
We will attack with the alps
as the wolves attack the herd
Your command, sir
And then, Osman?
You say they are five times larger than us.
What happens after we wipe out the first troop?
They won't realise we came to attack.
I will go in with the alps,
take Turgut Bey, and get out.
If Nayman was at their head,
he'd stop them from coming after us.
But they'll be eager to give
Osman Bey's head to Nayman
...and when they come after us...
I will take them.
And I will wipe out those who come from the straits
that we set up beforehand.
When the soldiers go out, the
headquarters will be defenseless.
And then...
From the south...
Bala Hatun, you and
the cavalry will charge.
Alright, Osman Bey.
Malhun Hatun.
You will attack with
infantry units from the north
We will definitely collapse their world.
It will be a tough war.
We didn't think otherwise, my Bey.
Eyvallah, eyvallah (thank you).
The remaining troops
will be with you, Aktemur.
As you order, my Bey.
You have shown us how we will attack them.
But how can we achieve victory?
Will these attacks be enough
to wipe out an army five times larger than us?
The things that will wipe out the headquarters
are in the hands of the Mongol soldiers.
They have stockpiles of weapons
and explosives in all four corners.
And when we explode them,
they will split into four arms
Then we will destroy them.
Well, when we are all in this war,
Yenisehir will be unprotected.
My Orhan.
Son.
While Orhan, son of Osman Bey, is in Yenişehir,
who says that it will be unprotected, mother?
Praise be!
Don't worry about it.
Praise be to my son.
That's my son.
Everyone get ready in the morning.
In these lands the sun will shine
only on believers.
He first made you take the fake gold.
And then he told me that
you had the gold.
And he sent me here.
Thus, you were going to kill me, and
thus he would have rid of his enemy.
Osman thinks he's smart.
But I will hit him from
the place he trusts the most
You are here and so are we.
What if he attacks Inegol?
What if he attacks your headquarters?
Olof, Osman scared you so much.
I dispersed all their armies
and took their weapons from them.
What will they attack?
I'm not afraid of anyone, Commander.
But underestimating Osman
will lead us to make mistakes.
The old owner of your castle
Turgut has fallen into my hands
And I will cut off his head if
Osman makes any small mistake.
Send a messenger to Inegol.
And let your army come here
early in the morning
Why?
We will unite your army with the Mongols
soldiers in the headquarters and...
...we will march towards the tribe of Osman.
And then Yenişehir, and then
we will erase everything related to the Turks.
There is only one end
for those who want to trick me.
Massacre!
Turguts head will go to Osman's tent
before we do.
Beautiful.
Yeni Sehir.
Alps, Hatuns.
Today is the day of battle.
Today is tournament day.
Today is the day of shahada.
Even if their number is more than us...
We are the brave ones.
We have faith.
- Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest!
Praise be to Allah,
Praise be to Allah!
And now our banner is up.
Sons.
You'll take care of our land
after we leave.
Your lands are our lands, my Bey.
We will protect at the risk of our lives.
Return with victory, my Bey.
Thank you.
May Allah bless you.
- Boran.
- My Bey!
-Bring me that dog!
-You command, my Bey.
Osman Bey.
My alps and horses are waiting ready
in front of the gates of Yenişehir
If you'll allow me,
I also want to come with you, Osman Bey.
Let this be your last change of sides,
Oktem Bey.
And know that you have no place behind me
if you make any wrong choice after this.
Okay, my Bey.
Olof will avenge for me, Osman.
As for me, I was fighting against
infidels like you Muslims and...
Shut up...
The infidels have always fought us.
They have always wanted to kill our call.
But their end is apparent.
And this will be your end.
- Boran,
- My Bey.
-Now send this to Olof
-As you order, my Bey.
Let's go!
May our battle be blessed!
I bear witness that there is no God but Allah, and
I bear witness that Muhammad is His servant and Messenger
Do you hear, Turgut?
They want your blood
You are now our guest
That's why the arrow hasn't
hit your forehead yet.
But when Neiman commands...
I have great ideas for you!
The real guests are you.
And you'll understand
when I kill you with my own hands.
But don't be sad.
You'll see neither the demolish of your
headquarters nor the death of your soldiers.
And they, too, will not see it.
These are very challenging sentences
for a man whose hands are tied.
When the order comes,
I'll put the rope around your neck
I will ride your body on my horse
You will, won't you?
Soon your unbelieving feet will
not be able to take a step on this earth
It will happen very soon
Soldiers!
Set the fire for the caldron.
And when Nayman comes back,
we'll throw Turgut Bey in it.
Come on, Osman Bey.
Come here
I know you will come
While our father is fighting
this difficult battle...
there is no room for us to make mistakes,
even for a moment, my brother
We will keep here safe.
Of course, brother.
We keep our promise.
Even if my arm that
won't hold anything anymore...
I still must triumph over
the healthy arm of the infidels.
So that I can fulfill
the promise I made to my father.
So that our nation rises.
Orhan Bey.
Everything you say will happen.
Of course it will happen.
And your arm will become
stronger than before, if Allah permits.
I'm your brother
And I know you more than yourself.
I know that inside you is burning.
My brother.
While you show toughness to everyone...
I know that you are afraid that
your arm might not be the same again.
But let your brother say something.
Your arm will be stronger than before.
My valiant brother.
Your brother will not collapse.
And this arm will certainly
become stronger than ever
And I will punish
whoever was the reason for this
That's my brother!
But we are not all talk.
Kumral Abdal will help.
We will practice.
I will never slack, brother
Come on, Alps!
Come on.
Come on!
Praise be to Allah!
Did you think I wouldn't come?
I had no doubt, brother
Catch them!
Don't let them escape!
O Allah
Are you fine?
I am.
-I am fine, thanks to you, Osman Bey
-Praise be to God
Beware.
They will want revenge.
Their pride will not tolerate this,
they will not leave us alone.
No, we are the ones who
will not leave them alone
Most of the soldiers are now
riding to Konur's trap.
Allah is the greatest!
Come on, alps.
Now we will go to destroy the headquarters.
May our conquest be blessed!
May Allah accept our martyrs
- Amen, amen!
- O Allah!
Let's go!
Alps!
The field is ours now!
O Allah!
Let's go!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is eternal!
Do you know the story of
the lion and the wolf?
In all the stories you tell...
There will always be a lion and a wolf,
Kumaral Abdul
Right, brother?
No.
You don't know this.
This is the story of the black wolf.
This wolf thinks of his people
before everything.
He lives for his followers.
He comes to the aid of all
those who fall into distress.
Doesn't every hero have an enemy?
There was an arrogant lion...
...ruling the other side of the forest.
That lion...
He lives for himself.
And he ignores his followers
for his desires and requests.
It is the severity of vanity and
arrogance that afflicted him.
He wiped out all his followers.
He set his sights on the kingdom of wolf.
Meanwhile, what do you think
the wolf did?
What did the wolf do, valiants?
He will not care about the size
of the lion and will punish him.
It is very difficult for
the strength of the wolf to defeat the lion.
He needs another way.
A different one.
Let everyone do their job!
Oh Right!
Hatuns.
Thank Allah, thank very much.
Many of them have run away, my Bey.
Let them.
They are the sign of our victory.
Let them run away so that they can speak of
our victory wherever they go.
Let them go.
Allah is the greatest!
Thank God!
Thank God, we won!
Thank Allah! Thank Allah! Thank Allah!
Take our wounded and martyrs
to the tents quickly.
We will increase our guard ten times!
Even twenty times!
We pulled out those dogs' teeth!
But they will continue to attack!
- Boran!
- My Bey!
Collect all the loot!
Look around the headquarters
We will never leave the right
of the oppressed to Nayman
Come on,
come on, brothers.
Thank Allah.
Wolves roam in
groups, Kumaral Abdul.
Doesn't this black wolf have a group?
It's the end of the world.
Even his group left the black wolf.
He has one solution left.
What is it?
He will hit the lion on his arrogance.
The lion was thinking of hitting the wolf.
But he did not expect that
the wolf would attack his forest.
That wolf would loot his belongings.
What happened, Komral Abdul?
The black wolf set the lions against each other.
And while they are fighting each other...
The wolf entered the lion's forest.
The wolf hit lion on his arrogance.
What is the reason for this victory, Komral Abdul?
Those who deserve to live the most
are those who risk their life.
The weakness of a lion and
the courage of a black wolf.
These brought the victory.
Thank Allah very much, I hope the story ends
this way all the time.
Hopefully.
Kumral Abdul.
Tell us about the loot.
What did the wolf get?
Who?
Who did this?
Osman.
Your death will be at my hands
Are we going to let Osman go away
unpunished, Neiman?
Osman got us down at his game, Shaman.
I will rip out his heart with my own hands!
May God witness my words!
I will water the earth with his blood!
His children and alps!
I'll take them from him one by one!
Yeni Sehir
Praise be to Allah.
May your hands and hearts be blessed.
We've done a lot of damage to the
Nayman's army without the Beys' alps.
Thank Allah.
Tell me, Boran, what's up?
My Bey, thank Allah,
we have killed many Mongol soldiers.
Half of the number we killed escaped.
Nayman's most skilled guard soldiers died
in the blast.
Praise be!
We call this a victory, Osman Bey,
but half the army is still alive.
Certainly this is a victory
It is the biggest victory!
It is evidence of the possibility of the small overcoming
the great, and the few over the many
And the possibility of the oppressed
prevailing over the oppressor.
And what will happen now?
The soldiers will be afraid
and their hearts will tremble.
They will constantly
think if we attack them.
What about the people of the tribe?
They will have the courage
They will say that he who is said to be invincible
has been defeated
And they will want to join
this blessed army.
Thank Allah, my Bey.
Praise be to Allah.
Thank Allah.
My Bey!
When will we have the wedding?
Let the preparations begin
as soon as possible, we've got the girl.
No sense in waiting anymore.
Doing such a good deed in the
blessed months is much acceptable.
May Allah. bless them.
Amen
Sogut
Osman did it while we were in Konya.
Nayman will be here shortly.
Osman.
He poked the hornet's nest.
He destroyed Nayman's headquarters.
Shall we increase our protection,
Mother Sultan?
That will make Neiman more suspicious, Celali.
He would question
if we're in this or not.
Mother!
Are you also in this
game, Mother?
Did you know about Osman's
raid on my residence?
Soldiers!
Put your sword back in its nest, Celali.
Nayman is not our enemy.
I told you, Mother Sultan.
Either you end the resistance.
Or I will take
your son's head first and then yours.
And then the whole Konya and all borders!
You didn't find Osman with us
when you arrived.
This is the whole reason.
Osman is like couch grass.
When he's among us, he poisons us all.
He has no place in our unit.
There will be no resistance, however...
...I am not responsible for Osman Bey.
When the donkey dies on a mountain...
...the damage falls on the owner,
Mother Sultan.
The price for what he did
will be paid by all of you!
I will not pay for what Osman Bey did!
Have no doubt on this!
My hatred for Osman Bey
is more than your hatred for him.
And if the Beys were involved
in Osman's plan.
Tell them, I am, this time...
I'm not only going to take their children.
When Osman stole the gold from you
He had declared war on all of us.
And when the Beys learns this
They will know that the one who
harmed their children is Osman.
That's not enough, Mother!
Nayman!
Despite everything,
our promise to you remains.
Your taxes and gold will come to you.
You collect gold, however...
What Osman pays can only be his head now.
I will turn these lands into a lake of blood.
This is what you deserve.
Such charitable acts
are more acceptable in good months.
I want to give the booty
we took from Nayman...
...to our people.
It's a very good idea, Osman Bey.
Always help your followers.
Eyvallah.
Our Lord, who made us reach
these three months of goodness...
...shall honor us with the arrival
of the month Ramadan, Inshallah.
- Amen.
- Inshallah.
Sheikh grandfather.
I don't know how, but...
the pleasure of praying and reading
the Qur’an is completely different...
...when we enter the three months.
Do you feel the same way?
Just like this world has
four different seasons...
...these three months are a period
that touch our heart.
Each one has a
different meaning and effect on the soul.
The duties of the human
differ in each one of them.
For example...
The three months...
They are the months in which
the reward is like a flowing waterfall.
Whatever you do,
God will multiply it for you
God's mercy is multiplied
for His servants in these months.
The three months are the months of pardon
and forgiveness for the servants.
Our Lord forgives His servants a lot.
It is the months in which our
Lord forgives His repentant servants.
We must do what we must do.
We will pray often.
And we will worship a lot.
And we will repent a lot.
So that...
We are absolved of the sins
we have committed throughout the year.
And get rid of the sins we committed.
To be good Muslims.
Not just for ourselves
In fact, for the sake of the nation of
Muhammad, all of us will be good Muslims
For Kayı, and for Yenişehir
For the sake of the Islamic world
and for the whole world
We will be good Muslims
And even for the infidels.
Because it is easy for infidels
to see the right when we are good Muslims
A Muslim is defined by his/her way of life.
Our life will be so beautiful and clean
that the unbeliever will long for it.
And the oppressor will be
ashamed of their injustice.
For this reason,
we must value our worship.
We will move away from lies,
hypocrisy and lack of justice...
...as we stay away from the fire of hell.
So that we show the truth beautifully...
So that our words affect even the unbeliever.
You're right, my sheikh.
It is not enough to talk about it.
The important thing is to live it.
These months are an opportunity
for all of us.
It is an opportunity to live as Muslims
and get rid of the sins we have committed
Don't waste this opportunity
With sincere repentance,
we repent with faith and hold fast to our worship.
I hope so my sheikh.
This is what we intend,
May Allah let us reach our intentions.
- Amen.
The three months herald us for the feast.
They announce the feast, so...
Let us receive it with a
beautiful religious chant.
Dear Boran.
Of course, my sheikh.
Eyvallah.
My Bey.
Play your Komuz.
Your command, my Bey.
You hit me
The fire of love and adoration of Muhammad
Muhammed
I am for you.
I am for your love.
Muhammed
I was struck by the fire of love
and adoration of Muhammad
I am for him, the path of Muhammad lover
Those who are his nation
constantly praise and praise Allah.
Make me a lover of Muhammad.
Put the love of Muhammad in my heart
And make me a lover of Muhammad only
I was struck by the fire of love and
adoration of Muhammad
I am for him, the path of Muhammad lover
And leave me as a lover in his way.
And make me crazy about Muhammad.
He always carried his nation's
concern and did not enjoy anything
You are the dignity of this nation,
O Muhammad
I was struck by the fire of love
and adoration of Muhammad
I am for him,the path of Muhammad lover
He called for the forgiveness
for the sins of the nation, that King of Kings
We have no fear on the day of punishment,
thanks to Muhammad
Honor me with your kind generosity, O Allah
Add a drop of Muhammad's sea to me
I was struck by the fire of love
and adoration of Muhammad
I am for him and the path of Muhammad lover
Wipe your black face with the footprints
of the virtuous teacher (refers to Muhammed)
If he is kind to me,
he will let me see Muhammad
His late community want to see him on earth.
Will it be easy to meet
the dust of Muhammad's feet?
I was struck by the fire of love
and adoration of Muhammad
I am for him,
the path of Muhammad lover
I was struck by the fire of love and adoration of Muhammad
I am for him, the path of Muhammad lover
Visit our website for more: turkision.com